Hello everyone.
Gain is gibnial.
My name is Kosaku Koizumi.
I'm Kosaku Koizumi.
My name is Jun Muto.
Gain is Sakaue.
Pleased to meet you.
By the way, everyone.
It's sudden, isn't it?
It's urgent.
Do you like games?
I love games.
You love games?
Yes, I do.
I don't have much of an image of you as a canary.
But... I...
I'm not very good at these electronic games.
I'm not very good at them.
But you'll buy it.
I'll buy it! I'll buy it!
Don't say that to me, too.
I'll buy them.
But I quit right away. I quit right away.
I love Rhythm Shiritori.
I don't need to use anything.
I don't care if there's no electronics.
I'm not good at electronic games.
Today's game isn't electronic.
You did it!
No electronic games...
What are you talking about?
I've prepared three non-electronic games.
Oh, my God! Yes!
Ending
Please subscribe to our channel!
- So, that means the three of us will be playing games today.
- I see. - Yes!
- First of all, we're going to play a game called "Nanjamonja". Wow, that's great!
- I don't know what it is yet.
- I've never played it before. - No, I've never played it either.
- I've heard a lot about a game called "Ha!
- I've heard a lot about it, but I've also seen it on variety shows.
- And the Nya-Nya game, which I played on the Stardust Channel.
- I played it on the Stardust Channel.
- I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it.
- I've done it, me and maybe Junko have done it - I've done it.
- games. - So let's see where we start.
- We'll do three of these, and then compete for points.
- I see. - That's interesting.
- That's interesting. - Well, I want to win this one.
- I want to win. Whoever wins the most wins.
- Happy. - And sad if you lose.
- Sad. - Yes.
- Which would you like to start with?
- Well, I don't know the rules, only "Naja Monja".
- Heh...
- On the contrary... but it's the easiest to understand.
- It's the easiest one, isn't it? It's a game called "Ha".
- Oh, really? - I've never played it.
- But it's pretty famous, isn't it? - Yes, it is.
- Okay, let's start with a game called Ha.
- Yes. - What's that?
- I'll explain the rules of the game.
- Can you play? - Well, it's a game called "Ha".
- I told you.
- No, no, no, you're right, it's that kind of game.
- That's what it is. That's what it is. That's what it is.
- Okay, we'll use these two cards, first.
- The yellow card? - One is the
- Act card.
- Act card. - Act.
- You can only say "Ha" in this game.
- By the way, the other card is a subject card.
- The other one is the subject card.
- What we're going to do now is to use these two cards.
- Let's try it once.
- First, you draw a card from the subject card.
- And I am a cat.
- You can only say this word at this time, this turn.
- So, I am a cat.
- So, I am a cat...
- So, this is the subject. - It's a subject.
- So, then you draw an act card one by one. - Act card.
- Then one, yes. - Then one, yes.
- One by one, yes. - Okay, one by one, yes.
- Okay, I'll draw.
- I'll draw. - Yes, me.
- I'll draw.
- And I'll show you. I'm not done yet.
- I'll show you. - I'll show you.
- This is a card that only you are allowed to see.
- This is a card that only you are allowed to see. Here are the letters of the alphabet.
- And it's got my alphabet on it.
- If I draw an A, for example.
- For example, if I draw an A, I have to say it like a great writer of the Meiji era.
- So, one by one, you say.
- And then one by one, you have to guess what ABCDEFGH this person is saying.
- You guessed right!
- So, isn't this a little difficult?
- It's hard. I can do it with a cat.
- I drew "H", but the real cat is "I am a cat".
- What do you mean?
- Try it. Try it. Try it.
- What do you mean, "Try it. Try it." So why don't you just put the meow-meow-meow game in there?
- Oh, meow, meow, meow, meow.
- What do you mean?
- What do you mean? I know exactly what you mean.
- It's like that.
- So if it's an "H" game, if Kousaku draws an "H" game...
- We'll be lucky if Kousaku gets an H. It's easy to understand.
- Oh, so that's how it is.
- That's how it is.
- Let's try it once, with all of us watching.
- I'm G.
- I'm a G. Yes, G.
- I'm E.
- Let's do it like that. Okay, I'll do it first.
- I'll do it like that.
I'm a cat.
I was trying to make it sound like that.
BAKAR!
You didn't cut that part.
That's not the point.
So, first of all...
I said, "What did you think I was doing?
I said, "Oh, well, I understand.
Then, you listen to me and follow me.
And if you guessed it, you get a point.
Right.
Okay, okay.
It's a simple rule now.
Okay.
Let's do it. Game 1.
Let's do it, game one.
Okay.
Okay, I'll draw first.
Here's the theme.
Raw oats, raw noodles.
Raw egg?
That's a mouthful.
Hey. - What?
What?
You say that twice in a row?
You say it twice in a row? This one.
That's a fast word.
Wow.
So when you say it like that...
I'll need my acting chops.
Oh, no.
It's not so much acting ability.
Expression.
It's about enthusiasm.
First of all, enthusiasm.
I'm talking about enthusiasm and expressiveness.
Wow.
Well, that's because acting ability is also important.
That's right.
I'd like to do it first.
What? This is the first question?
Seriously?
I'm impressed.
Yes, sir.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, okay, minute.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
First you play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
5You could show
Importantes
One more question.
Just a minute.
rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, scissors
raw egg
Raw punya
And then...
One more.
Stage
Raw barley, raw rice, raw eggs, raw barley, raw rice, raw eggs, raw eggs
Yes, yes, yes.
You were a little sloppy, weren't you?
Well, well, well, well, well.
Here we go.
Raw barley, raw rice, raw eggs.
What's that? Could it be...
Wow!
Hey, which way?
I don't know anymore.
Okay, then.
Okay, you got it?
It's decided.
Let's start with the order in which they lived.
Okay.
Crafts.
I thought crafts were easy.
Here, let's do this one.
Let's do it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Here we go.
Ready?
Okay.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
The correct answer is
E.
Oh.
Well, that's easy. This is...
This one.
That's what we're doing.
Okay.
Next, Jun.
Ready?
A.
I was...
I was A.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'll do it.
Good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's great.
I'll do it.
I'm in.
Ready?
D
Eh, something's different.
Oh.
Don't react like that.
I'm serious.
You're making me nervous.
All right, everyone gets two points for this one.
Oh, that's not so bad, is it?
A thousand a time.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
You guys are good.
Good, good, good, good.
Okay, I'm going to save the shuffle craft.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Okay, next subject.
Okay.
This is important!
This is important.
That's important.
That's what acting is all about, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Oh, no, that's not good.
Roll the father twice.
No, not this one.
Dad... like dad...
It's not a fast word.
Not twice.
Huh.
Shall we go then?
Okay.
Shall we?
Okay, then.
Act Card
Yes, sir.
Yes!
Oops.
Aah!
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, Ayuu, one more time.
Yes...
You're good, but you'll lose.
Wait a minute.
Yuu, we're doing it anyway, right?
Gugugu at first.
It's like a jaggy
A game of "ayuh"...
All right!
Joon, you're first.
Yes, sir.
Gugugu first.
It looks like a jaggy.
Last one.
Here we go.
Dad...
It's too hard.
Wait a minute.
It's too hard!
I think we're splitting up.
I'll go.
I'm in.
Dad.
What?
What? Which one, which one?
Oh, no. Mwah.
Wow, but...
It's spicy. It's spicy.
Spicy think, spicy think.
Dad, what?
Aren't they all the same dad?
All three of them have something in common, don't they? Maybe.
Maybe they all have the same alphabet.
Okay, let's see.
No, wait, I think I got this right.
So, you're Jun.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Okay, have you decided?
Yeah, we're set.
Ready, B!
Wow, that's easy to understand.
I'm B.
I'll go like this.
Oh, so that's why E?
E.
The correct answer was E.
Yes!
You did it!
I haven't seen that face in 10 years.
That's the first one. That's the key.
Your father was the key.
If you've been paying attention, it's a little spicy, isn't it?
He hated me a little bit.
I didn't see that part.
I didn't see that.
He was using a lot of sticks.
Oh, no.
I thought it was time to protest.
I haven't seen your face in 10 years.
Wait a minute... but, the point is...
The point...
How many candidates are there?
No, I don't either.
Seriously.
Okay.
I've decided.
Ready, C!
A!
No, I was torn between C and F, too.
F, F.
Which one's C?
C is me.
I'll take F.
A.
F.
Wow, that's the one!
I'm so happy!
I was just about to...
I was kind of begging for it.
You're right about everything!
But it's hard to tell because they're from the same lineage.
That's right.
It's one or the other.
Well, I thought Kaname had a sweet face.
Oh, so you mean?
Oh, OK.
Okay, here's my answer.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
You've decided on the canary.
I've got it.
Ready, A!
C!
What?
When C was begging for it.
I thought he was thinking of my dad back home.
The correct answer is A.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, man!
Oh, my God!
No, this is... this is what I thought of my dad back home.
This is not good.
When I got here, it was a real pain in the ass.
I was on the train in the evening, and the train doors opened, and I was like...
He was like a father to me.
Oh, I see.
He was your father.
You know what, let me show you the difference.
I haven't seen your father in 10 years.
I haven't seen him in 10 years. I'm just supposed to cry.
Well, you're right.
It's easy to understand.
You're right, you should go there.
I'm just thinking of him as a father who's in the process of getting ready to say, "Hey, I really need a favor.
He's such a serious guy.
Dad, no, but here's the thing.
Well, so far I've answered all your questions correctly.
Really?
I got one.
Oh, two?
No, no, no, three.
Four, three, two.
There you go.
There we go.
Oh, no.
Same to you, Junko?
I'll draw.
Here's the theme.
Oh, that's it...
I haven't heard that in a while.
I haven't heard this in a while.
This is the hardest thing I've heard in a long time.
It's so hard!
You know, it's hard because they put something similar in the "A" through the "H".
This one's hard.
Every time, I don't understand the first part...
I'm probably out of ideas here.
No, I'm out of H.
It's hard.
But this is pretty good.
B and G are the same.
Now that I've done it, I'm thinking... facial expressions are important.
Yeah, facial expressions are important.
There's a lot of information you can read from facial expressions.
It's true, but it's only three letters.
I don't know how much you can convey in three letters.
I'm going to use four letters.
"Nah.
It looks like a "na-".
Stretch it out.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes...
Well, well, well, well, well...
The one you don't want me to come to is here.
First, a rock-paper-scissors-scissors game
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Yes, same as before.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
He's always so strong.
Okay, let's start with Jun.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Okay, then.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, I'll go.
Oh, hey.
What?
Oh, shit!
Yuck.
Wow!
Okay, okay, I'll go.
I'll take that one.
Oh, it might be good.
Okay, let's start with Jun-kun.
Jun-kun, that was easy.
No, I messed this one up. I'm sure of it.
Well, guess what?
No, I'm just like Jun-kun.
I'm like Jun-kun.
I got one. Okay.
Ready, C.
Then I got a B.
You've got to be kidding me. I'm pretty sure that's not it.
Oh, man, I must have misread it.
I think I got the B one right.
Oh, I must've misread it. I was...
You were one down. I was one up.
Seriously.
This often happens when I play games with Jun-kun.
Yes, I was looking at the bottom row.
I don't know what to do.
What am I supposed to do?
I'll take a closer look at this. Seriously.
Okay, well, anyway, this was a mistake.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
I didn't read that far. We were wrong.
Mistake, mistake, mistake.
Jun-kun, zero points.
I'm sorry.
Okay, yes, I'll go.
The first one.
Okay, okay, okay, I got this one.
I got two pairs, just in case.
Ready, go!
Oh!
No, it was this one and the royal A.
Yeah, no, that one and that one. I was torn.
Nice item.
No, it's hard, isn't it? A and E. It's hard.
Oh, yeah.
Crafting
So, I'm thinking
I think I can do crafts, too.
Okay, let's do it.
G!
That's it.
That was a D.
Oh, that way.
That one.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll do it after I see the other subjects.
That's right.
It's the same.
I don't think it's the same if it's just for the sake of it.
No, we're the same.
I know that feeling.
It's so fast-paced... one at a time.
That's for sure.
I don't know if they'll understand.
I don't know if they'll understand. Then I'll start by empathizing with them.
That's it!
That's it.
What? That's it?
I'll go lighter.
That's it. That's it.
That's it.
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit, right? That's it.
That's it! That's it!
Jun's a little different.
Well, well, well, D, I've got no choice.
I'll go.
That's it.
Sho, that's it!
Shouzu, that's it...
That's it...
It's soooooooooo cool.
Here we go.
That's it!
Cool!
That's it... that's it...
I'm sure it'll be different if I guess this one, but...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
You've got the wrong intonation.
I'm at a loss. It's the hardest thing I've ever done.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Joon's habit is very strong.
What a game!
Mr. Jun has a strong habit.
I don't like it.
I've done three questions.
I'll give you the points.
I only missed one, so...
One point for me.
I got both wrong.
I got 5 points.
That means...
Three.
Three times three, five.
So...
I'm strong!
I win the game of haha from now on!
Wow.
I'm kinda...
Beatable
I'm with the wrong guy, too
I'm so disappointed.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's one up from the other one.
Oh, yeah.
But still.
It was a lot of fun.
Well, the game is called "Huh" and it's like this.
But there's more.
There are two more.
That's right.
I want to play this with everyone!
Members!
It'll be fun!
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
meow
yes
Ajimemama
Jang jang jang!
Mojamoja abercut
Aaaaah!
Wow!
That's awesome!